<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Wade Johnson</title>
    <link>https://hooskers.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Wade Johnson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hooskers.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://hooskers.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hooskers.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>PDX Live Transit PDX Live Transit consists of a backend piece and a frontend piece that use Trimet&amp;rsquo;s Realtime GTFS API to show all of their vehicles in the Portland metro area on a map in realtime.
The backend is a simple Express server that has JavaScript code compiled from Realtime GTFS protobufs. All it does is get the vehicle positions from Trimet&amp;rsquo;s endpoint, marshals it to JSON, and sends it to the client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://hooskers.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hooskers.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Experience Front End Developer NetXposure, Inc. Digital asset management company in Portland, Oregon
2018 - Present
 Implemented new features and fixed bugs filed in Jira for the front end (Backbone.js SPA) and the back end (Java server/RPC API) Migrating Backbone views to React - Designed render prop component that updates when a Backbone collection/model event is triggered to increase React/Backbone code abstraction Updated Jenkins pipeline to provide greater stability and finer controls for builds Optimized webpack config which decreased build times from ~30 seconds to ~20 seconds per dev build  QA Engineer NetXposure, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>